Finding Aid for the Joseph Byrne Lockey Papers LSC.0127
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Central America
  - 67. Wyke
    - Wyke to Russell. Comayagua, November 23, 1859.; 11.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/102 no.7 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
  - 68. Duplicates (State Department)
    - Title page, vol.68., 1.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Buchanan to Marcy -, January 22, 1856.; 2.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.144). (Box 4)
    - Buchanan to March, February 1, 1856.; 3.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.117). (Box 4)
    - Title page, vol.17., 4.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Cass to Dallas, April 1859.; 5.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Cass to Dallas, August 12/59.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.189). (Box 4)
    - Title page, Nicaragua Dispatches, vol.1., 7.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Bozland to Marcy, August 28, 1853.; 8.; 13pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.3). (Box 4)
    - Bozland to Marcy, October 8, 1853.; 9.; 6pp. (Copy typewritten, of S.D. no.6). (Box 4)
    - Bozland to Marcy, January 11, 1854.; 10.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. no.12). (Box 4)
    - Title page, Great Britain Dispatches, vol.69., 11.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Squier, E. George to William Brown Esq. M.P, March 19, 1856.; 12.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Brown, William to [Unknown], March 20, 1856.; 13.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, March 21, 1856.; 14.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.2). (Box 4)
    - Squier, E. George to [Unknown]. London, March 23, 1856.; 15.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Brown, William to [Unknown]. Fenton's Hotel, March 24, 1856.; 16.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, March 28, 1856.; 17.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.3). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, April 29, 1856.; 18.; 8pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.7). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, May 23, 1856.; 19.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.10). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, May 27, 1856.; 20.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.11). (Box 4)
    - Squier to Dallas, May 28, 1856.; 21.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, May 30, 1856.; 22.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.12). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Squier, June 1, 1856.; 23.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, June 3, 1856.; 24.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.13). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, S.D., no.15., June 13, 1856.; 25.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, July 1, 1856.; 26.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.18). (Box 4)
    - Dallas to Marcy, July 11, 1856.; 27.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.19). (Box 4)
    - Proposed article, n.d.; 28.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D.). (Box 4)
    - Title page. State Department, vol.8., 29.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Marcy to Lord Napier, May 29, 1857.; 30.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Title page. State Department, vol.3., 31.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Savage to Marcy, October 31, 1853.; 32.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.18). (Box 4)
    - Savage to Marcy, November 10, 1854.; 33.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D., no.19). (Box 4)
    - Title page. State Department, vol.16., 34.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Marcy to Dallas, March 14, 1856.; 35.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Marcy to Dallas, April 7, 1856.; 36.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
    - Title page. State Department. vol.2., 37.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 4)
    - Squier to Dlayton, October 10, 1849.; 38.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 4)
      - Declaration. Enclosure 38 above., 1.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - October 10, 1949). (Box 4)
  - 69. Squier
    - Correll, Ruth E. The Mission of Ephraim George Squier to Central America., 1.; 27pp. (Copy, typewritten, of term paper, n.d.). (Box 4)
- Florida
  - Horn, Andrew H. - History of the Americas, Class Notes. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence and reports of Governor Patric Tonyn and others, 1782-85. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence and reports of Governor Patric Tonyn and others, 1785-88. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence and reports; East Florida subsidies and 1790 subsidies, 1788-90. (Box 7)
  - Correspondence and reports, 1790-1801. (Box 8)
  - Diary of John Hambly, 1794. (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and reports, 1802-17. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence and reports, 1817-19. (Box 10)
  - Archives General de Cuba, Legajo 151A, 1877, 1900, 5555, 5559, 5560, 5562, for the years, 1787, 1815-19. (Box 10)
- Manuscript of Book
  - East Florida, 1783-1785: Select Documents for the History of Florida., With an introduction, translations, and annotations by Joseph Byrne Lockey, Ph.D, 1942. (Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15)
- Florida, Miscellaneous
  - Petition of Denys Rolle to the Lords of His Majesty's Privy Council for relief from hardships attendant upon his attempt to form a settlement in East Florida )., (Late 18th Century (Box 15)
  - Report of John Gerar William De Brahm on his surveys of the coast of Florida, Georgia, and South Carolina., Included is a list of the inhabitants of East Florida and their professions from 1763 to 1771. (Box 15)
  - Notes from Dr. Lockey's class, History 162A & B. (Box 15)
  - A collection of forty letters from Dr. Lockey to Dr. Robert W. Frazer, 1939-1946. (Box 15)
  - One cardboard box of index cards with notes. (Box 16)
- Microfilm
  - Microfilm. (Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20)